It's VGT, Wave Gotik Treffen in Leipzig, one of the biggest goth festivals and I'm sick.
I spent all day at the camp yesterday laying around on the couch.
I definitely had other plans for this festival and this video instead of like being sick two days.
But I will show you some impressions nevertheless. Have fun!
I didn't wait for you
I just carried on up the mountain
Because I craved for you
I worked hard and realized
There's no comparison
The books are explanations
so since I'm not feeling very well I am spending a lot of time at the camp this
big itty by the way this is my tent and I'm standing here in the cooking tent
because guys are cooking this festival so let's see what we have for dinner
today. Okay, so first this is going to keep everything warm all day. We have
pasta with, I don't know, some kind of sausage. We have tomato sauce and pasta
without sausage and also some homemade couscous salad. Yummy! And this is a long
long table with all kinds of beverages and food and drink.
And this is all of our camp. We have three pavilions and one is for cooking
basically and all the tents. The weather, this festival is beautiful.
And I'm hoping to get better soon and show you some more of the festival.
Somebody ought to know
Where do we go?
Ain't it funny how
How much we take for granted
When with everything
It never worked hard or realized
If you gotta let go then maybe that's for the better
You can't feel the rain when you're holding an umbrella
And you can't see a smile without looking in the mirror
So where do we go?
If we could take our time
Into the bottom line
I'd really like to know
So where do we go?
Somewhere that I know
I don't want to waste your time
But somebody ought to know
Where do we go?
you